[
  {
    "question": "Who is the protagonist in the movie 'Iron Man'?",
    "answers": ["Thor", "Black Widow", "Captain America", "Tony Stark"],
    "correct": "Tony Stark",
    "questionId": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Thor's enchanted hammer?",
    "answers": ["Mjolnir", "Stormbreaker", "Excalibur", "Nidavellir"],
    "correct": "Mjolnir",
    "questionId": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which infinity stone does Vision possess in 'Avengers: Infinity War'?",
    "answers": ["Mind Stone", "Reality Stone", "Power Stone", "Space Stone"],
    "correct": "Mind Stone",
    "questionId": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the main antagonist in 'Black Panther'?",
    "answers": ["Killmonger", "Thanos", "Loki", "Ultron"],
    "correct": "Killmonger",
    "questionId": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the real name of the superhero 'Black Widow'?",
    "answers": [
      "Natasha Romanoff",
      "Wanda Maximoff",
      "Carol Danvers",
      "Jessica Jones"
    ],
    "correct": "Natasha Romanoff",
    "questionId": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Guardians of the Galaxy', what is the name of Star-Lord's ship?",
    "answers": ["Millennium Falcon", "Quinjet", "Slave I", "Milano"],
    "correct": "Milano",
    "questionId": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character says 'I am Groot' in 'Guardians of the Galaxy'?",
    "answers": ["Rocket", "Drax", "Groot", "Star-Lord"],
    "correct": "Groot",
    "questionId": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the director of 'The Avengers'?",
    "answers": [
      "Christopher Nolan",
      "Joss Whedon",
      "James Cameron",
      "Steven Spielberg"
    ],
    "correct": "Joss Whedon",
    "questionId": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the villain in 'Ant-Man'?",
    "answers": ["Yellowjacket", "Red Skull", "Ghost", "The Vulture"],
    "correct": "Yellowjacket",
    "questionId": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Doctor Strange', what mystical artifact does Doctor Strange use?",
    "answers": [
      "Eye of Agamotto",
      "Soul Stone",
      "Cloak of Levitation",
      "Book of Vishanti"
    ],
    "correct": "Eye of Agamotto",
    "questionId": "10"
  }
]
